Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1996-131
  - Fu, Irene H., Age Structure of the California Tiger Salamander (Ambystoma californiense) Population at Lake Lagunita: influence of Rainfall and Water Management Practices on Annual Recruitment.., March 1996 (Box 2)
  - Fullerton, Anne, Daily Activity Rhythms of the Harvester Ant, Pogonomyrmex barbatus, in Response to Changing Environmental Cues.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Gove, Nathan A., Seeking Development and Survival Differences in Colias larvae which are linked to variation in metabolic enzymes.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Gupta, Naveen, The Role of Vasodilators and Vasoconstrictors in the Growth inhibition and Apoptosis of Cells in the Cardiovascular System.., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Hagan, Catherine E., Concentration Measures of Volatile Anesthetics in the Aqueous Phase using Calcium Sensitive Electrodes.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Ho, Cheryl June, Understanding the Role of DWnt-2 in Drosophila melanogaster Thoracic Muscle Development.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Hong, David K., Regulatory Pathways of B-Amyloid Precursor Protein and Presenilin-1 in Microglia and other Immue-Response Related Cells.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Hwang, Bryan J., Epileptiform Activity Associated with an Experimentally Induced Microgyrus: a Model for the Cortical Malformation of 4-Layered Polymicrogyria.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Hwang, Dick, Cloning the whirligig non-complementing gene.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Jones, Maggie, Investigation of subcellular localization of IRKI in the Schwann cell of the sciatic nerve of the rat; failure to establish a transfectant model system in MDCK cells.., March 1996 (Box 2)
  - Kan, Tin-Na J., Expression Pattern and Regulation of Protease Nexin-l in Mammalian Cerebral Cortical Development.., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Kazemi, Mahmood Reza, Stabilization by Bovine serum Albumin of Antibody-Conjugated Paramagnetic Liposomes Used in the Magnetic Resonance of Cell Adhesion Molecule Expression.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Kim, Eva Christina, Zinc Porphyrin Photoreactivity in the Presence of Surfactants.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Kim, Jean M., Isolating enhancer elements of the A-agouti isoform of the mouse agouti gene through lacZ expression studies.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Kiriakos, Lindsay, Conspecific Fighting in the Red Harvester Ant Pogonomyrmex barbatus.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Kwan, Kristen, Functional Analysis of GDI Isoforms.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lam, Alan S., Expression of Moesin in Regenerated Hepatocytes after Partial Hepatectomy.., June 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lam, Chris T., Reconstructing the Phylogeny of Taiwanese Aboriginal populations Using Microsatellite loci.., May 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Catherine Tung-Ling, Enhanced Expression of the 5B-Tubulin Isotype in K562 Cells as a result of Treatment with Paclitaxel., May, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Eurie, The Recombinogenicity of a Novel DNA Targeting Intermediate of Homologous Recombination., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Marc J., Differential Growth of the Teleost Retina., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lewczyk, Julie, Stable Autonomous Vectors for Cystic Fibrosis Gene Therapy., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lien, Cindy, Synthetic Lethal Interactions with CIN4, a Gene Involved in Yeast Microtubule Function., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Joseph, Modulation of Bovine Articulation Chondrocyte Collagen mRNA Expression with Hydrostatic Pressure., May, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Peter T., Isolation and Molecular Characterization of Mutants in Synaptobrevin, a Synaptic Vesicle Protein in Drosophila melanogaster., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lyo, John Kyungjin, Work Towards Isolation of hypersprouty, a Gene that Regulates Secondary Branching in the Drosophila Tracheal System., March, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Mao, Julie, Different effects of dopamine uptake inhibition and Norepinephrine uptake inhibition of EEG Wake and REM sleep in Narcoleptic canines., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - McGrath, Tory, Misregulation of a Drosophila Homeotic Target Gene by the Human Oncogene E2A-PBX1., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - McNiff, Ceara Coleman, Investigation of Altered Proliferative Potential in an Arabidopsis thaliana Mutant, gax, by GFP-Promoter Fusions., June, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Osmanian, Cynthia, Hypoxia-induced apoptosis and the selection of apoptotically-deficient cells in solid tumors.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Paige, Michael Thomas, Probing structiral transitions of peptide dissociation from proteins of the class II major histocompatibility complex.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Ray, Kimberly, Regulation of nanos translation.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Rhodes, Justin S., Social influence on sex determination in the African cichlid fish, Astatotilapia burtoni.., August, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Rocca, Monique E., The effects of elevated carbon dioxide on flower attractiveness and phenology in Lasthenia californica.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Ruffy, Mauro B., Searching for an alternatively spliced form of Rskla in Zenopus laevis.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sarkar, Urmimala, The generation of interleukin-4 secreting, insulin-specific T cell hybridomas from nonabese diabetic mice.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Shih, Leo, Growth comparisons of pabB mutants of Salmonella typimurium, in vitro.., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Singh, Meetpaul, Study of ion transport mechanisms in a human lung cell line., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sohn, Samuel M., Characterization of abd-A versus Ubx functional specificity in Drosophila melanogaster.., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Sohoni, Aparna, Characterization of adhesion molecules mediating follicular localization of murine B cell lymphoma BCL1.., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Stevenson, Derek, Squid locomotion: size limitations on effective and efficient swimming., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Suster, Maximiliano, Transcriptional Activiation by the Drosophila Myb Protein.., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Tjioe, Daniel, There is no relationship between Apolipoprotein E e4 Allel Dosage and Rate of Decline in Alzheimer's Disease.., May, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Tran, Hien Tranh, Characterization of the photochromogenic gene(s) of Mycobacterium marinum.., June, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Christine D., Identification of Proteins Regulating the Drosophila Decapentaplegic Enhancer Using a Yeast Expression System.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Wee, Sue Ann, Pilus null mutants show abnormal fruiting body morphogenesis in Myxococcus xanthus.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Whitson, Heather, RNA ploymerase II position at a DNA damage site: role in transcription-coupled DNA repair.., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Tyler S., The Drosophila misguided gene encodes the nuclear lamin DMo and is required for proper guidance of terminal tracheal branches.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Wong, Esther, The role of interleukin-7 in the regulation of Kappa light chain gene rearrangement in pre-B cells.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Wong, Kenneth, Using mismatch repair detection (MRD) to identify DNA sequence variation.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Yoon, John, The characterization and differentiation of osteoclasts from macrophage precursors in tissues harvested from revised joint prostheses.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Yuan, Tara, Iron accumulation in maturing mouse astrocyte cultures increases their vulnerability to oxygen-glucose deprivation.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Yun, David K., An attempt to isolate superrepressing TRAP mutant of bacillus subtilis.., June 1996 (Box 5)
  - Yung, John, Assaying for Arabidopsis and Maize cDNA Sequences involved in pre-mRNA Processing using a yeast genetic screen.., June 1996 (Box 5)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1997-120
  - Anandasabathy, Niroshana, Conservation of Secretory Machinery Between Yeast and Mammals: Sec6 and Sec8 Mammilian Homologues Localize to the Basallateral Membrane of MDCK Cells., May 23, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Banerjee, Ronadip, Saccharomyces Cerevisiae Replication in the Double Strand Break Repair Complex., May, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Baron, Elinor, Human Skin Fibroblasts Expressing the Human Papillomavirus E6 Gene are Deficient in Overall Genomic DNA Repair and Sensitive to UV Radiation., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Ian, Elucidating the role of passively acquired maternal antibodies in protection of neonatal mice against homologous rotavirus infection., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Cathcart, Alice, The Effect of Differential Resource Availability on Female Oviposition Hostplant Choice in the White Cabbage Butterfly, Pieris Napi.., May, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Bryna, Asymmetrically Localized Proteins and Mitotonic Cleavage Orientation in the Developing Rodent Cerebral Cortex.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Jeffrey, A Detailed Atomic-Level Approach to Protein Fold Recognition.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Eric, C-Myc Activation Reduces Plating Efficiency in Rodent Fibroblasts Through an Apoptotic Mechanism that can be Suppressed by a Soluble Paracrine Factor.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Harvey Robert, Increase in the Activity of Matrix Metalloproteinases During Flow-and Hypertension-Induces Arterial Remodeling.., May 23, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Johathan W., Functional Comparison of Class I MHC Antigen Presentation Between Bone Marrowgenerated Dendrtic Cells and Spleen Dendritic Cells Through a Mouse Hybridoma Model.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Jonathan Hong, Biochemical and Immunological Characterization of Novel 150kD Extracellular Matrix Basement Membrane Protein Recognition by Monoclonal Antibody 7A10.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Ludy C., Overexpression of PMC1, A Vacuolar CA2+ Atpase, In Mutants Lacking Vacuolar H+ Atpase Activity (VMA Mutants) Improves Growth On Calcium and FK 506.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chew, Teri, using pGex Glutathione S-Transferase for the Production of Anitbodies to Astrovirus ORF la.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chin, Raymond, Role of T Cell Mediated Immune Processes in Lossening and Osteolysis of Total Hip Replacements.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chiu, Bill, Search for the "Hourglass" Gene, a Midgut-Specific Regulator of HOX Gene Expression.., May 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chou, Vivian H., A Deletion Mutant in the Human Cytomegalovirus Gene Encoding IE1491aa Fails to Block TNF-alpha-induced Apoptosis in Human Fibroblasts.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Chuong, Edwin T., The Construction, Expression, Purification, and CHaracterization of a Mutant Hen Egg Lysozyme., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Dacey, Claire R., The Impact of INsect Herbivores on the Competitive Success of Nitrogen-Fixing Plants and the Contribution of Symbiotically Fixed Nitrogen to the System.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Didwania, Aashish, Identification of the Active-Site Residue In Human Adenovirus Protease Serotype 2.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Doctor, Vishal Shishir, Human Phylogenies Derived from Haplotypes Composed of Simple Sequence Polymorphisms Linked with an Autosomal Microsatellite.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Domin, Alexander, RecA Mediated In Situ Hybridization to Genomic DNA with Biotyinylated Oligomers.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Eiken, Patrick Wade, Isolation and Characterization of ospA Regulatory Mutants in Rhizobium meliloti.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Harper, Courtney, Regulatory Sites Within the -1286 to -1640 Upstream Promoter Region of the bcl-2 Proto-Oncogene in Human B Cells.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Heidary, Shahriar, Hyperglycemia Stimulates Specific Protein Kinase C Isoforms and Superoxide Production in Human Aortic Smooth Muscle Cells.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Ho, Jason S., Regulation of Blimp-1 Expression in B Lymphocytes and Plasma Cells.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Hoerner, Michelle, The Effect of Astrocytes on the Phagocytosis of Myelin by Macrophages.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Hong, Robert, Nest Relocation in Response to Light Stress and Water Deprivation in the Argentine Ant (Linepithema humile).., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Huang, Wilmer, Mapping and Cloning of Stumps, a New Drosophila Gene Required for Tracheal Branching.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Hurley, Patrick, Factors Affecting the Nest Success of the California Towhee: Spatial and Temporal Variation in Brood Parasitism and Nest Predation.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Jacobs, Alice A., Tangential Neuronal Migration in the Developing Cerebral Cortex.., May 23, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Gregory G., The Effects of Anti-CD43 Monoclonal Antibody Immunotherapy on the Genesis of Diabetes in NOD Mice.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Josephson, S. Andrew, Characterization of a Bicyclomycin Resistance Mutation Altering Transcription Termination Factor RHO of Escherichia Coli.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Jung, David Hyun, Overexpresison of patched results in changes in neural tube gene expression: conservation of the hedgehog-patched signalling pathway.., May 1997 (Box 2)
  - Kaung, Geoff, Degredation of the T Cell Receptor Alpha Subunit By the Proteasome.., May 1997 (Box 3)
  - Kim, Paul Joseph, Employing Broad-Range Primers to investigate Bacterial Association with Atherosclerosis.., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Krvstkowiak, Andrew J., In Vivo Smooth Muscle Cell c-fos Gene Expression During Flow-Induced Arterial Remodeling.., March 1997 (Box 3)
  - Kumar, Himanshu, Identification of Differential Cortical Gene Expression in the Ground Squirrel Brain During Hibernation.., May 1997 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Edward B., Inflammation and Alzheimer's Disease: B-amyloid Induced Production of Inflammatory Cytokines and Nitric Oxide by BV-2 Microglia., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Gi Soo, Variation in the Territorial Behavior of the Marine Patellacean Limpet Lottia Gigantea., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Kimberly J., Identifying High Risk Patients for Epstein-Barr Virus Associated Post-Transplantation Lymphoproliferative Disease., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Li, Rhoda Han-Yu, The Ecology and Biology of Colobonema sericeum (Vanhoffen 1902), a Deep-Sea Trachymedusa, in Monterey Bay, California., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Mary, Fibroblast Gowth Factor Receptors in the Developing Mouse Cerebral Cortex., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Ma, Jae H., Ontogenesis of Circadian Sleep-Wakefulness Rhythms in Rats., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Maas, James, Mechanisms of Signal Transduction Leading to Neuronal Apoptosis in Retinal Ganglion Cells., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Madani, Kamyar, Interferon-Gamma Cooperates With Members of the Tumor Necrosis to Induce Apoptosis in the Epithelial Lung Cancer Cells., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - McClory, Vasey, Tissue Distribulation and Subcellular Localization of mRNA from Four Recently Cloned K+ Channel cDNAs (SqKvlA-D) in the Optic Lobes and Stellate Ganglia of the Squid, Loligo opalescens., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - McMorrow, Meredith, Maternal and Infant Health Care Policies in the U.S. and France: Do Social Welfare Benefits and Universal Health Care Provisions Affect National Health Indices?., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Meezan, Joshua D., Characterizing and Comparing Carbonic Anhydrase Activity in Calu-3 Human Airway Cells and Other Cultured Cell Lines: Is There a Connection to Basal Chloride Current?., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Munro, Elizabeth, Oligodendrocytes Promote the Survival of Central Nervous System Neurons In Vitro and In Vivo.., May, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Nguyen, Jackie K., Production and Characterization of Monoclonal Antibodies Against Procine Bone Marrow Cells.., May 1997 (Box 3)
  - Nilsen, Geoffrey B., Rhythms of Rod Progenitor Cell Division in Organotypic Slices of Haplochromis burtoni Retina.., March 1997 (Box 3)
  - Oak, Jack, An In Vitro Studv of the mRNA and Protein Expression Levels of Basic Fibroblast Growth Factor and Macrophage Chemoattractant Peptide of Scratch Wounded Astrocytes.., May 23 1997 (Box 3)
  - Pai, Shan, Isolation of GIP194p, a Protein that Interacts with Human y-Tubulin, Using the Yeast Two-Hybrid Screen.., June 1997 (Box 3)
  - Pang, Phillip S., Redox Potential Stablilzation by the Polypeptide in the Heme Protein Myoglobin.., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Papanastassiou, Alexander, Detarmination of Interleukin-6 and Soluble Interleukin-6 Receptor in Cerebrospinal Fluid From Multiple Sclerosis Patients.., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Pittson, Sky, Anesthetic Effects on Gaba and Glutamate Synapses.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Rabinovici, Gil Dan, Ischemic Modulation of Cortical Micro-EEG Activity in Rat Brain Slices.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Randle, Steven, Inter-Individual Variation and Effect of Wave Height, Tidal Height, Time of Day, and Season on Foraging Upon Mussels by the California Sea Otter, Enhydra lutris.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Shaevitz, Marejka H., Differential Display as a Method for the Isolation of Beta Islet-Specific Autoantigens in Insulin Dependent Diabetes Mellitus.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Shen, Katherine, The Effects of Activated p21-ras on differentiated Liver Functions., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Srinivasan, Priya, Out of Africa: A Genetic Study of the Migratory Route of Homo Sapiens Using the Tamil Population of South India.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Sun, Bryan, The Use of Polymorphic Microsatellites to Determine Genetic Relationships between Language Isolates and Neighboring Populations., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Tierney, Emily, Regulation of IGF II by Trophoblast Derived Growth Factors and Cytokines during invasion.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Tran, Alyssa, Re-Targeting of Retroviral Mediated Gene Therapy to Activated T Cells.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Tran, Doan, Expression of the C. elegans FKH/HNF-3 Transcription Factor lin-31 Requires Multiple Positive and NEgative cis-Acting Regulatory Elements.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Troie, Sergiu Zgripcea, Cexamethasone Induces the Expression of C-IAPS and Caldesmon in the Human A549 Adenocarcinoma Cell Line: Possible Mechanisms for Inhibition of Interferon-Gamma and Anti-FAS-induced Apoptosis.., May, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Kevin Chun-kai, Characterization of the Segment Polarity Gene Naked in Drosophila melanogaster: a Novel Antagonizer of Wingless Signaling.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Raymond Yu-Jeang, The V5 Region of BII Protein Kinase C has a Higher Affinity Than the BI PKC V5 Region for the RACK1 (Receptor for Activated C Kinase) Protein.., February 1997 (Box 4)
  - Wong, Brian, Photic Regulation of Vasoactive Intestinal Polypeptide mRNA within the Mouse Suprachiasmatic Nucleus.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Wright, Paul M., Regulation of Contact Rate in the Argentine Ant, Linepithema humile.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Wu, Henry Tsung Ming, Development of HIV-Derived Gene Therapy Vectors.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Xiao, Lily T., Differential Production of Interleukin 12 in Allergic and autoimmune Inflammatory Disorders.., May 1997 (Box 4)
  - Yen-Wei Lin, Michael, Identification of Regions Interacting With hermaphrodite, intersex, and doublesex to Reveal Potential New Genes Involved in Sex Determination in Drosophila melanogaster.., June 1997 (Box 4)
  - Yu, David Sung-Wen, The Induction of Rosenthal Fiber Stress Proteins in Cultured Astrocytes.., May 23, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Zhang, Miao, The Role of Nitric Oxide in Aseptic Loosening With and Without Osteolysis.., May 1997 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1998-283
  - Bartos, Blythe, Transmission of Helicobater pylori Through Varying Water Types: An Experimental and Observational Study., May 27, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Berberian, John, Leukocyte Migration Into Lacrimal and Salivary Glands in an Experimental Model of Sjogrens Syndrome., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chien, Amy, Cloning of Capon: A Gene Espressed in all Layers Except Layer 4 of the Adult Rat Cerebral Cortex.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chu, Felicia, Neuroleptic Drug-Induced Shape Changes to Human Erthrocytes.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chu, Stephen, Characterization of the Dynamics and Function of a NOvel Golgi Membrane Skeleton.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Chung, Nancy, IL-12 Does Not Promote Blood-Brain Barrier Breakdown Following Vesicular Stomatitis Virus Infection of the Central Nervous System., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Cortopassi, Karen, Glucocorticoid Modulation of Stressor-Induced Activation of Antioxidant Exzymes.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Davidson, RecA Mediated Targeting of css DNA to Super coiled Duplex DNA: Effects of Target Sequence Heterology on Multistranded Hybrid Intermediates of Recombination.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Edson, Eleanore, Testing the Role of Calcium Channels and PKA in Late-Phase Long Term Potentiation.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Eriksson, Carl, Repression of hEGF Expression by the Tetra-Repressor.., June 1998 (Box 1)
  - Farber, Adam, The Role of the B7-CD28 Path way in Osteolysis and Aseptic Loosening of Total Hip Replacement.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Feng, Felix, The Neuronal Trafficking of the alpha2A and alpha2C Adrenergic Receptors.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Ford, Beneranda, Heme Oxygenase Expression and Maturation in the Neonatal Lung.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Gupta, Anurag, Gene Therapy Using the Rat Brain Glucose Transporter Gene Alters Mediators of Necrotic Neuron Death.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Hall, Allison Haberstroh, Effects of Blocking Action Potential Activity on Axonal Pattern Formation in Slice Cultures on Ferret Cerebral Cortex.., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Hays, Allison, The Control of Cell Proliferation at the End of Neurogenesis in Developing Rat Cortex.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Henderson, Amy, Stimulation of Adenosinergic Al Receptors Modulates Respiration-Determined Sleep States in the Very Young Neonatal Rat.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Himmel, Allison, An Electrophysiological Investigation of Anesthectic Effects at Excitatory and Inhibitory Synapses in the Mammalian Brain.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hong, James, Systemic Analysis of Sleep Architecture: REM cyclicity is intact in canine narcolepsy.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hoppe, Bradford, Complementation of the radiosensitive M059J cell line with a DNA-PKcs gene.., May 22, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Howard, Sarah A., Hormone Modulation of gp120 Neurotoxicity Cascade.., March 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hsieh, Joseph Chia-yu, Overexpression of glucose transporter or bc1-2 protects hippocampal neurorns against kainic acid excitotoxicity.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Iyer, Asha M., Glucocorticoids Exacerbate gp120-Induced Neurotoxicity in Striatal Cultures.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Pieter T., An investigation of abnormalities in amphibian communities: evidence for parasite infection as a cause for super-numerary limbs and other limb deformaties in Hyla Regilla.., May 22, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Joshi, Nirav, Characterizing the Mechanism of Entrainment in Siberian Hampsters (Phodopus sungorus).., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Kamangar, Salar, Identification of PCNA as the cell cycle target in HLA-derived immunosuppressive peptide.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Kao, edward Yao-Ting, Macrophage Colony Stimulating Factor Augmentation of Beta-Amyloid-induced Interleukin-1, Interleukin-6, and Nitric Oxise Production by Microglial Cells.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Khandekar, Melin, Characterizing the distribution of Cystatin B in the brain of Mus musculus using in situ hybridization and Immunohistochemistry.., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Khurana, Rahul, Contribution of the aroF promoter to trp operon expression in Baccilus subtilis.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Michael Sanf-Hak, Antinociceptive Response to Transcutaneous TRanscranial Electrical Stimulation (TCES) is Frequency-Dependent.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Kuo, Christin S., Characterizing Mammalian SNARE (SNAP receptor) Interactions Mediating ER to Golgi TRansport.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Kwok, Joe, Inter- and Intra-Species Specific Variations of Human and Simian Beta-defensin 1.., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Lam, Alison M., Characterization of Synapse Formation and Development During Synaptogenesis in rat Hippocampal Neurons.., June 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lao, David, Phosphorylation of CD34 and Transmembrane Signaling in Human Dermal Microvascular Endothelial Cells (HDMEC)., May 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lau, Camilla K., The Expression Patterns of EPH Receptors and Ligands in the Developing Rat Brain., May 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Ernest E., Differential Gene Expression in the Teleost Retina: Day vs. Night., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Jennifer Yunhee, The Fidelity of Chromosome Segregation in Old vs. Young Yeast Cells., May, 1998 (Box 3)